I thought
if I just endured everything in silence,
it would all be over.
I thought
if I helped Song Yanfei
finish the dance drama,
it would all be worth it.
But I was too naive.
In the eyes of those rich people,
I'm just an innocent kid.
No,
I'm just a fool.
They can play me for a fool
however they want.
Can I leave now?
Of course you can.
I hope you keep your word,
Mr. Feng.
Shen Xi,
are you really stupid
or just too naive?
What do you mean?
Shen Xi, you can't be like this.
You'll easily get scammed wherever you go.
No wonder you drifted in Beijing for years
and achieved nothing.
Fine.
Where's your brother?
I'll teach you a lesson today.
Cut the crap.
What do you mean?
Look at you,
getting anxious again.
Does being anxious help?
Actually, it's nothing much,
but there's one thing
you haven't figured out.
I'm
just a messenger.
The one who really
decides the championship
and the prize money
is our boss,
Gao Yuhai.
What did you say?
I asked you,
what did you say?
Nothing much.
You were willing to sleep with me.
So I just
went with the flow and slept with you.
And tested you out for our boss
while I was at it.
You did pretty well.
You'll be in our boss's bed
in a couple of days.
Just be a little more flexible.
Oh, right.
Don't be too forward.
Our boss
doesn't like girls who are too flirty.
Is there any need to play
the innocent girl with me?
There's a saying,
one wrong step
leads to another.
I know I'm already in too deep
and there's no turning back.
So I thought,
I'd just bear
all the misfortune alone.
Since it had come to this,
I might as well
win the championship and the prize money
to help Song Yanfei
finish his dance drama.
Three days later,
Feng Shu took me to a place.
I remember
it was a Saturday.
It had already started raining at dusk.
By nightfall,
there was lightning and thunder.
It was terrifying.
We're here.
Let's go.
Where are we?
Why do you care?
All you need to know is that
after tonight,
you'll get everything you want.
Maybe even more.
As long as you show our boss a good time.
Let's go.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up.
Go.
Hurry.
The boss thinks highly of you.
Let's go to the wine cellar.
The wine cellar?
Don't worry.
It's a nice place.
Let's go.
Come in.
Follow the red carpet
all the way to the end.
The boss is waiting for you inside.
Let's go.
Mr. Gao,
Come in.
Stop right there.
Turn around.
Look at me.
Mr. Gao,
Come here.
Take a good look.
Mr. Gao,
Is this okay?
Kneel.
Kowtow.
Mr. Gao,
I...
I know.
You need money urgently right now.
Just do as I say,
and the dance competition
prize money is yours.
And this money
will be yours too.
Okay.
I'll kowtow.
Wait a minute.
First, say
you are willing to serve me in her place.
I am willing.
To serve Mr. Gao in your place.
Kowtow.
Now say
you are willing to always
respect her as the lawful wife.
I am willing.
To always respect you as the lawful wife.
Kowtow.
Say you are willing to be
Gao Yuhai's mistress.
I am willing to be
Gao Yuhai's mistress forever.
Louder.
I am willing to be
Gao Yuhai's mistress forever.
Kowtow.
Get up.
Get on the bed.
Strip.
Leave nothing on.
You are the lead actress
of this dance drama,
and also its investor.
Without you,
this dance drama wouldn't exist.
And there wouldn't be this memorable...
great moment.
It was also her who won
the dance competition
and the prize money,
which made the release
of this dance drama possible.
Here, I want to say...
Shen Xi,
marry me.
Okay.
I'll strip.
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei, Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Special Appearance
(in order of strokes of Chinese surname)
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Feng Shu, Liu Yakun
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Bai Sha, Li Xintong
Mu Liyan, Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei, Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Gao Yuhai, Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Forensic Doctor Cheng
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Liu Haohan
Young Li Xingchen, Li Yuanche
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Young Song Yanfei, Chen Nuoyan
Investor, Zha Minxin
Lead Singer, Xu Weina
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Gao Jingman
Xiao Ze's Mother: Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Relatives: Li Ming, Wang Zhilei
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Guest Female Classmate: Yue Yue
Yao Sha
Li Xingchen's Classmates:
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Woman: Sun Meili
Nanny: Wang Chunyang
Shareholders: Huang Xinyang, Wang Wentao
Gao Yuhai's Secretary: Du Du
Feng Shu's Secretary: Dai Dai
Drivers: Wang Yiguo, Liang Hui
Old Man Walking Bird: Wang Jiasheng
Waiters: Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Aunties: Tu Manxia, Huang Xinyang
Middle-aged Man: Wang Xinda
Driver Old Zhao: Wei Hong
Xiao Ze's Father: Zhou Wen
Speaking Girl: Yue Yue
Liu Junjie
Driver: Hu Huazheng
Scrapyard Boss Zhang: Li Chenghu
Company Head: Bai Yongjun
Female Nurse: Bai Wanting
BBQ Restaurant Guests:
Cheng Gong, Qiu Yaqiong
Guo Xinye
Speaking Man in Black: Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in: Zhao Peng
Li Xingchen's Stand-in: Tang Li
Song Yucheng, Liang Zhengchao
Cashier: Wu Tiantian
Yan Yongmei, Li Tianjun
Actor: Hu Zexuan
Cleaner Liu
Extras: Da Qing, Liu Haohan
Receptionist Xiao Yu: Ren Jiefei
Crew
Chief Presenter: Xu Yue
Co-Presenters: Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Planner: Li Meina
Chief Distributor: Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant / Original Story: Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producers: Sui Dalong, Gao Jingman
Producers: Sui Sanlong, Li Xin
Executive Producers: Peng Xia, Kang Hairu
Planner: Zhao Feng
Production Manager: Liu Zhilong
Daily Life Producer: Yin Zhongheng
Liu Xinyu
Finance: Geng Yusa
Grip Team
Key Grip: Liu Yiqing
Tang Qunbao
Kitchen
Kitchen Manager: Yin Xiumei
Vegetable Washer: Hu Xiuxia
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Zheng Xiaorong
Zhang Meijuan
Liang Hui
Song Shuwei
Xiao Yucai, Liu Xin
Screenwriter: Yue Shunming
Script Supervisor
On-set Assistant Director: Liu Haohan
Editing Team
DIT: Jin Linxin
Sound Team
Sound Assistants: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Production Designer: Zhao Daqian
Co-Production Designer: Gong Xueyuan
Executive Art Director
Assistant Art Director: Wang Tianyi
Props Art Director
Props Master: Sun Donghua
On-set Assistant
Li Yao
Set Dressers: Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
Director of Photography Li Yixu
Camera A Operator He Yong
Camera A Assistant Li Xinghan
Camera B Operator Zhao Shidian
Camera B Assistant Cao Xing
Camera C Operator Ma Mingguo
Camera Operator
Camera Grip Guo Ruicai, Liu Shihao
Behind the Scenes Li Chen
Lighting Director Gao Yun
Te Rigun
Styling Team
Hair & Makeup Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
On-Set Wardrobe Supervisor Zhang Lei,
Yi Junli
Promotion & Distribution Team
Planning Director Yang Liuting
Graphic Design
Post-Production
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Coordinator Zhang Xiaoman
Niu Xuerui
End Credits Jin Linxin
Re-Recording Mixer Zhang Kai
Ambience Editor Zhang Xinyu
Sound Effects Editor Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
Production Supervisor Gao Dong
VFX Executive Jin Linxin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Hong Kong Musical Theatre, China
Music Director Xiao Zhuang
Score Production Xiao Zhuang, Wang Dafu
Music Coordinator Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Score Mixing Zhao Yi
Vocal Recording Zheng Suyang
Song Recording Studio
Beijing Landuo Recording Studio
"Brothers"
Vocals Yue Shunming
Arranger Zhao Yi
Vocals Zhang Keying
Yu Xiaotong
Composer Xiao Zhuang
Producer
"Promise"
Composer Xiao
Vocals Ben Damiao
Lyricist Xu Yue
Composer Xu Yue
Vocals Xu Yue
Arranger Wang Anyu
Lyricist Fan Fan
Producer Xu Yue
Lyricist Bai Yuxiang
Xiao Zhuang
Composer
"Only You" (Russian)
Vocals Liu Ruixun
Composer Xiao
Arranger Zhao Yi
Publicity Department
of Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Hubei Zhiyuxuan Agricultural
Technology Co., Ltd.
Hubei Jiutouniao Catering
Management Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Dongfeng Hometown Historical
Materials Exhibition Hall
Shiyan Xiaowujia Catering Management
Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Maojian District Sunshine Dance
Art Training School
Meiyijia Convenience Store, No. 88
Gongyuan Road, Zhangwan District, Shiyan
Co-Production Companies
Sichuan Jiaodian Pictures Co., Ltd.
Sichuan Prism Chuangjie Film
and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.